and try, you know, to get her over
on checking me I have to ask one
ask Marie Eh it feels like you
looked at me pretty hard today actually
No now so Now I thought Yes I checked
around everyone here Yeah okay So man
only Thus feel in and feel of and
must be
loyal to each other because I felt today
that it started to spread and I became little
not sure about you Kelda that where you were
somewhere and you can't
this [ __ ] staircase
hell and already after day one it was
full speed murder and lies everyone wants
the money itself AB
[Music]
it straight up and down I want out before
Yes exactly exactly and especially safe then
if they show that they can sort of screw up
to that little because she doesn't have
lied but she has kind of So she said